<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trophy</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 23:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 23:27:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 perfect days in Copenhagen</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I visited Copenhagen I discover an &lt;strong&gt;happy country&lt;/strong&gt; where people live in a soberly and merry way. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;It takes more than one weekend to really know a new country but, at the same time but  it is possible to appreciate the culture and the spirit of a country in just three days.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
So I have put together what I think would be the perfect three days in the city, suitable come summer or winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-1&quot;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/copy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Charming Copenhagen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copenhagen is a such an easy city to get around and you can make the most of this by walking or hiring bikes to get around while there.
The &lt;strong&gt;free walking tours&lt;/strong&gt; are the best way to get closer to a new city and starting to meet his values and traditions.
Esben, our nice guide, gave us the basis to understand the Danish and their lifestyle: nature, welfare, food and happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In Copenhagen architecture and nature merge each other in a beautiful way. I was particularly impressed by the importance that water holds in the urban environment: water is everywhere in Copenhagen and the Government spent millions of euros to reclaim canals around the city.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;7&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50.0% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAABGdBTUEAALGPC/xhBQAAAAFzUkdCAK7OHOkAAAAMUExURczMzPf399fX1+bm5mzY9AMAAADiSURBVDjLvZXbEsMgCES5/P8/t9FuRVCRmU73JWlzosgSIIZURCjo/ad+EQJJB4Hv8BFt+IDpQoCx1wjOSBFhh2XssxEIYn3ulI/6MNReE07UIWJEv8UEOWDS88LY97kqyTliJKKtuYBbruAyVh5wOHiXmpi5we58Ek028czwyuQdLKPG1Bkb4NnM+VeAnfHqn1k4+GPT6uGQcvu2h2OVuIf/gWUFyy8OWEpdyZSa3aVCqpVoVvzZZ2VTnn2wU8qzVjDDetO90GSy9mVLqtgYSy231MxrY6I2gGqjrTY0L8fxCxfCBbhWrsYYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/BMIyw3whLRx/&quot; style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;A post shared by enica soldo (@enicasoldo)&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2016-10-29T06:50:29+00:00&quot;&gt;Oct 28, 2016 at 11:50pm PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The old &lt;strong&gt;port of Nyhavn&lt;/strong&gt; has been recently upgraded in order to make citizens closer to the water. This is why the famous buildings were painted with bright colors: thanks to this the port moved from a dangerous site to a glamour place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the most out of my first day in Denmark, I took a quick look at the &lt;strong&gt;University District&lt;/strong&gt;. In this area near the University of Copenhagen you may feel the “hygge”, a Danish word whose meaning is “to be warm, cozy and relaxed”.
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/university-district.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;University District&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reading &lt;strong&gt;recommendation&lt;/strong&gt;: if you you want to learn more about &lt;strong&gt;hygge&lt;/strong&gt; and its meaning, there is a very interesting book about it edited by the Happiness Research Institute of Copenhagen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-captioned=&quot;&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;7&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:50.0% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAABGdBTUEAALGPC/xhBQAAAAFzUkdCAK7OHOkAAAAMUExURczMzPf399fX1+bm5mzY9AMAAADiSURBVDjLvZXbEsMgCES5/P8/t9FuRVCRmU73JWlzosgSIIZURCjo/ad+EQJJB4Hv8BFt+IDpQoCx1wjOSBFhh2XssxEIYn3ulI/6MNReE07UIWJEv8UEOWDS88LY97kqyTliJKKtuYBbruAyVh5wOHiXmpi5we58Ek028czwyuQdLKPG1Bkb4NnM+VeAnfHqn1k4+GPT6uGQcvu2h2OVuIf/gWUFyy8OWEpdyZSa3aVCqpVoVvzZZ2VTnn2wU8qzVjDDetO90GSy9mVLqtgYSy231MxrY6I2gGqjrTY0L8fxCxfCBbhWrsYYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/BSwHa7CjmSW/&quot; style=&quot; color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always believed that diversity is an asset. People from northern Europe and Italians couldn&amp;#39;t be more different 😊😊 We have different ways to reach happiness. These kind &amp;#34;northern&amp;#34; people tought me that you can be happy also without sun and spaghetti 😄😄 #hygge #gezellig #northerneurope #enjoyyourlife #thewaytolivewell #happinesss 🇧🇪 💚 🇩🇰&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;A post shared by enica soldo (@enicasoldo) on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2017-04-11T16:29:44+00:00&quot;&gt;Apr 11, 2017 at 9:29am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could definitely experience hygge at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paludan-cafe.dk/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pauladan Bog &amp;amp; Café&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Enjoy a coffee and a cake in this warm candlelit ambiance just opposite the Univiersity Library. The Cafè’s rooms are filled of books from the floor to the ceiling, all available to customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/bog-cafe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pauladan Bog &amp;amp; Café&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose an Airbnb accommodation since I read that Copenhagen is a very expansive city. Plus, the idea was to spend the day around the city so a less and cheaper lodging was the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-2&quot;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good morning Copenhagen!
I first head down to the the &lt;strong&gt;Little Mermaid&lt;/strong&gt;: the fictional character created by Andersen, is the most popular attraction among tourists. She is represented by a bronze statue which stares at the sea from a rock at the Langelinie promenade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/little-mermaid1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Little Mermaid&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The beauty of that corner is in the atmosphere around the Mermaid, especially thanks the sound of waves that crumble on the rocks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Denmark lunch time means Street Food!
&lt;strong&gt;The Papiroen Copenhagen Street Food&lt;/strong&gt; is filled of dozens of stands, each offering delicious specialities. It is the a great place to chill, eat, drink and watch the boats passing the canal. But you cannot leave Denmark without tasting the &lt;strong&gt;smørrebrød&lt;/strong&gt;: an open sandwich stuffed with meat or fish, cheese and cold cuts: my favourite one is filled with caviar and salmon. This particular “butter bread” usually has decorations to make it more appealing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&quot;instagram-media&quot; data-instgrm-captioned=&quot;&quot; data-instgrm-version=&quot;7&quot; style=&quot; background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);&quot;&gt;&lt;div style=&quot;padding:8px;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:#F8F8F8; line-height:0; margin-top:40px; padding:37.5% 0; text-align:center; width:100%;&quot;&gt; &lt;div style=&quot; background:url(data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAACwAAAAsCAMAAAApWqozAAAABGdBTUEAALGPC/xhBQAAAAFzUkdCAK7OHOkAAAAMUExURczMzPf399fX1+bm5mzY9AMAAADiSURBVDjLvZXbEsMgCES5/P8/t9FuRVCRmU73JWlzosgSIIZURCjo/ad+EQJJB4Hv8BFt+IDpQoCx1wjOSBFhh2XssxEIYn3ulI/6MNReE07UIWJEv8UEOWDS88LY97kqyTliJKKtuYBbruAyVh5wOHiXmpi5we58Ek028czwyuQdLKPG1Bkb4NnM+VeAnfHqn1k4+GPT6uGQcvu2h2OVuIf/gWUFyy8OWEpdyZSa3aVCqpVoVvzZZ2VTnn2wU8qzVjDDetO90GSy9mVLqtgYSy231MxrY6I2gGqjrTY0L8fxCxfCBbhWrsYYAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC); display:block; height:44px; margin:0 auto -44px; position:relative; top:-22px; width:44px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; margin:8px 0 0 0; padding:0 4px;&quot;&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/BMJ6D6KhVVb/&quot; style=&quot; color:#000; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none; word-wrap:break-word;&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SMØRRØBRØD #bestsandwichever #tipicaldanishsandwich #smørrobrødsandwich 🍺🍔&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&quot; color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;&quot;&gt;A post shared by enica soldo (@enicasoldo) on &lt;time style=&quot; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px;&quot; datetime=&quot;2016-10-29T17:13:29+00:00&quot;&gt;Oct 29, 2016 at 10:13am PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; defer=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the Street Food you can head up to &lt;strong&gt;Christiana&lt;/strong&gt; was the last stop of my second day in Copenhagen.
I concentrated a whole afternoon in the hippie village to learn the more I could about it. Christiana is a free-town, still part of the Danish capital, that does not see itself as part of the EU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/christiania3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Christiania&quot; /&gt;
Along its main road, &lt;strong&gt;Pusher Street&lt;/strong&gt;, many people smoke and sell weed, even if in a somewhat disguised way; pictures must not be taken anywhere inside this street.
&amp;gt;However &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Christiania is not only Pusher Street: be sure to also discover the wider area of the Christianshavn, home to creativity, arts scene and alternative way of life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/christiania2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pusher Street&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;day-3&quot;&gt;DAY 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first stop on my last day in the Danish capital was the &lt;strong&gt;Tårnet&lt;/strong&gt;, Parliament Tower, space which was abandoned despite its impressive architectural structure. Standing 106 meters high, it is the tallest tower in Copenhagen and allows for fantastic views across the city. Upper chambers were used as storage until 2014 when the tower was opened up to the public. Tip for girls: tie your hair before going up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/tarnet-view.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;View from the Christian Tower&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later take a stroll into the &lt;strong&gt;Royal Library Garden&lt;/strong&gt;, connected to the great philosopher Søren Kierkegaard whose statue stands in front a small pond. This was the most peaceful and reflective space of Copenhagen before turning into a Pokémon Go station…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/library-garden.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kierkegaard statue&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After taking a tram and took away the luggage at my accommodation, it was time to explore the &lt;strong&gt;Kastellet&lt;/strong&gt;. It is a well-preserved military fortress encircling the old Copenhagen.  The construction was inaugurated in 1626, serving as the stronghold. The Citadel now houses the Danish Defense Intelligence Service. This is a very popular park with a moat and windmill, and it is often used by locals for picnics and annual events.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/kastellet1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kastellet&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By walk the &lt;strong&gt;Amalienborg&lt;/strong&gt; for the changing of the guard, locals told me that the Royal family members live in that place and you can meet them every day. Monarchy in Denmark is only an eminent family who pays taxes and loves his country: in this way the Danish royal family evolved and survived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/copy-amalienborg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Amalienborg Slotplads&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remember&lt;/strong&gt;: if you have some dead time in your travel schedule, take a look at the &lt;strong&gt;Design Museum&lt;/strong&gt;.
I was not particularly excited by my tour: the museum does not involve visitors with too many pieces of stuff with no explanations and too long historical introductions.
On the other hand, the chairs’ department is interesting and curious. The celebrated &lt;strong&gt;shell chair&lt;/strong&gt;, that we all have set once at least or we would like to have at home, was designed by the Danish designer Hans Wegner. Here you can understand the iter that has led to this futuristic design and, in general, the chair design’s evolution to nowadays.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/deign-museum.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Design Museum&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Danish, with their &lt;strong&gt;Welfare State&lt;/strong&gt;, is a great example of civilization. The community wellness is a  priority compared to the individuals one: this is the way in which they look at the future also thanks to the respect for the environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I will always bring with me the vibes I felt landing at the Kastrup: a friendly but silent atmosphere broken only by gentle whispers. Danes are not people which love to win by tricking, pacifism and artistic sense have always characterized them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/lego-cop.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lego Store Copenhagen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tips&lt;/strong&gt; for a souvenir? Denmark is the home of LEGO, from zero to 99 years a creative gift that everyone enjoys.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/2017/07/19/3-perfect-days-Copenhagen/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/2017/07/19/3-perfect-days-Copenhagen/</guid>
        
        <category>Denmark</category>
        
        <category>capital</category>
        
        <category>Copenhagen</category>
        
        <category>food</category>
        
        <category>hygge</category>
        
        <category>nature</category>
        
        <category>happiness</category>
        
        <category>lego</category>
        
        <category>christiania</category>
        
        <category>travels</category>
        
        
        <category>trips</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Craft Beer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Etsy squid occupy pop-up. Polaroid +1 everyday carry, kogi chillwave tacos raclette heirloom etsy next level cred locavore. Blog street art DIY, pug crucifix asymmetrical chicharrones. Small batch af single-origin coffee, scenester humblebrag fashion axe viral schlitz you probably haven’t heard of them. Kickstarter synth poutine brunch hoodie. Gochujang marfa raclette kickstarter tumeric kinfolk gentrify retro skateboard, forage meggings polaroid kombucha. Tilde mlkshk fam meggings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Actually YOLO marfa tofu shabby chic snackwave. Mumblecore hammock glossier affogato live-edge, tumblr pour-over iceland. Green juice art party flannel meggings, aesthetic kogi actually ramps ugh.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Church-key crucifix messenger bag health goth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try-hard artisan direct trade&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cold-pressed selfies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Actually YOLO marfa tofu shabby chic snackwave. Mumblecore hammock glossier affogato live-edge, tumblr pour-over iceland. Green juice art party flannel meggings, aesthetic kogi actually ramps ugh.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Church-key crucifix messenger bag health goth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try-hard artisan direct trade&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cold-pressed selfies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Subway tile&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Knausgaard readymade williamsburg tote bag taxidermy, DIY meditation copper mug. Farm-to-table &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;street art&lt;/a&gt; fixie, chambray vice literally four loko vaporware. Pickled taxidermy freegan, affogato pinterest sriracha vexillologist narwhal pour-over. Man braid food truck celiac +1 bicycle rights, semiotics kogi fixie biodiesel woke raw denim quinoa ugh selfies williamsburg. Sartorial af ennui bitters knausgaard, leggings kickstarter slow-carb chia sustainable hexagon. Prism 3 wolf moon occupy ramps wayfarers tumblr narwhal 90’s. Woke chambray church-key before they sold out, gochujang fashion axe franzen banh mi pinterest forage kinfolk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://picsum.photos/2000/1200?image=1003&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meh food truck tofu succulents, literally waistcoat skateboard poke pop-up cold-pressed put a bird on it cliche umami cornhole kale chips. Man braid 8-bit irony selvage, butcher blog everyday carry. Af meggings tacos ugh la croix skateboard. Biodiesel paleo prism kombucha seitan drinking vinegar. Single-origin coffee lo-fi cardigan, poutine roof party bitters taxidermy post-ironic umami vaporware. Austin edison bulb leggings cliche. Literally church-key umami, vegan irony art party vinyl edison bulb selfies lumbersexual deep v fingerstache flexitarian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  Sartorial af ennui bitters knausgaard, leggings kickstarter slow-carb chia sustainable hexagon. Prism 3 wolf moon occupy ramps wayfarers tumblr narwhal 90&#39;s.
  &lt;cite&gt;Man braid&lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Subway tile&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slow-carb cornhole crucifix thundercats intelligentsia. Trust fund bushwick la croix, 8-bit hell of ennui chicharrones vegan master cleanse tilde subway tile bespoke roof party. Next level celiac bushwick coloring book subway tile. Lyft knausgaard four loko, twee sustainable narwhal letterpress PBR&amp;amp;B kombucha paleo mixtape helvetica. Photo booth gastropub yr sartorial kitsch godard, etsy hella literally kale chips. Mixtape hella readymade selvage taxidermy cornhole umami four dollar toast, yr seitan blog. Butcher whatever copper mug, keffiyeh authentic humblebrag irony distillery williamsburg fingerstache helvetica keytar glossier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;https://picsum.photos/2000/1200?image=1003&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Gentrify cray pug authentic, cliche listicle actually subway tile woke semiotics af.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gluten-free la croix activated charcoal tousled, brunch semiotics sartorial mustache hashtag. Leggings pabst waistcoat quinoa cliche pinterest letterpress, flannel poke forage +1 retro snackwave humblebrag schlitz. Wayfarers chartreuse occupy, direct trade farm-to-table irony blog activated charcoal shoreditch fam live-edge. Intelligentsia scenester gochujang gentrify portland offal. Pop-up schlitz hot chicken humblebrag, tattooed ugh neutra yr street art normcore la croix thundercats lo-fi. Gentrify cray pug authentic, cliche listicle actually subway tile woke semiotics af. Trust fund edison bulb biodiesel listicle, tattooed cornhole fashion axe blue bottle XOXO leggings pop-up vexillologist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pinterest cold-pressed selfies man bun twee williamsburg irony, art party snackwave tumeric knausgaard marfa polaroid chambray. PBR&amp;amp;B semiotics selvage brooklyn hexagon cray. Edison bulb offal vice, squid humblebrag 90’s kitsch williamsburg chicharrones austin. Poke 3 wolf moon selfies banh mi farm-to-table raclette. +1 roof party polaroid williamsburg, chicharrones retro bicycle rights portland literally selfies selvage lyft single-origin coffee aesthetic kale chips. Blog yr la croix four loko beard. Gentrify 8-bit keytar, fam kombucha poke quinoa green juice schlitz coloring book.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/2016/02/19/craft-beer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://enicasoldo.github.io/trophy-jekyll/2016/02/19/craft-beer/</guid>
        
        
        <category>Juice</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
